{"data":{"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"2277","name":"Galaxy Coney Island","address":"13611 Grand River Ave","zipcode":"48227","owner":"Liz Gjergjaj","licenseNumber":"042592","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","mostRecentLicenseDate":null,"establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":"High","reviewFrequencyDays":"180.0","geom":"0101000020E61000000C06EFC26ECB54C08006E27C37314540","inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"44256","establishmentid":"2277","name":"Galaxy Coney Island","inspectionDate":"2018-11-27T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"112","pcount":"1","pfcount":"1","ccount":"1","criticalcount":"2","noncritical":"1","correctedcritical":"2","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"44256","inspectionDate":"11/27/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"2277","name":"Galaxy Coney Island","violationCode":"3-501.17","violationDescription":"(A)  READY-TO-EAT, POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  prepared and held refrigerated for more than 24 hours in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT  shall be clearly marked at the time of preparation to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\r\n(B)  A container of refrigerated, commercially prepared READY-TO-EAT POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  shall be clearly marked, at the time the original container is opened in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT, to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\r\n\r\nA date marking system that does not exceed 7 days, including date of preparation, or opening is to be used. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"In house prepared ready-to-eat potentially hazardous  food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Without date of consumption marking","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-11-27T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Datemark with a discard date of 7 days or less."},{"inspectionid":"44256","inspectionDate":"11/27/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"2277","name":"Galaxy Coney Island","violationCode":"3-304.14","violationDescription":"(A)  Cloths that are in use for wiping FOOD spills on TABLEWARE shall be maintained dry and used for no other purpose. \r\n(B)  Cloths in-use for wiping counters and equipment shall be held between uses in   a chemical sanitizer solution, and laundered daily.\r\n(C)  Cloths in-use for wiping surfaces in contact with raw animal FOODS shall be      kept separate from cloths used for other purposes.\r\n(D)  Dry wiping cloths and the chemical sanitizing solutions shall be free of FOOD    debris or visible soil.\r\n(E)  Containers of chemical sanitizing solutions shall be stored off the floor and         used in a manner that prevents contamination of FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, SINGLE-SERVICE, or SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.\r\n(E)  SINGLE-USE disposable sanitizer wipes shall be used in accordance lable               instructions.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Wiping cloth(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored on","subProblem":"Counter","location":"COOKING AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Store wiping cloths completely submersed in sanitizer."},{"inspectionid":"44256","inspectionDate":"11/27/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"2277","name":"Galaxy Coney Island","violationCode":"3-301.11","violationDescription":"(A) To prevent food contamination FOOD EMPLOYEES shall properly wash their      hands.\r\n(B) FOOD EMPLOYEES may not contact exposed, READY-TO-EAT FOOD with      their bare hands and shall use suitable UTENSILS such as deli tissue,       spatulas, tongs, single-use gloves, or dispensing EQUIPMENT. (P)\r\n(C) FOOD EMPLOYEES shall minimize bare hand and arm contact with exposed     FOOD that is not in a READY-TO-EAT form. (Pf)\r\n\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Employee(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Handled with bare hands","subProblem":"","location":"COOKING AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-11-27T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Suitable utensils or single-use gloves are to be utilized."}]},{"inspectionid":"42567","establishmentid":"2277","name":"Galaxy Coney Island","inspectionDate":"2018-06-04T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Complaint","inspectorid":"112","pcount":"0","pfcount":"0","ccount":"0","criticalcount":"0","noncritical":"0","correctedcritical":"0","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"42225","establishmentid":"2277","name":"Galaxy Coney Island","inspectionDate":"2018-05-08T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"112","pcount":"1","pfcount":"0","ccount":"1","criticalcount":"1","noncritical":"1","correctedcritical":"0","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"42225","inspectionDate":"5/8/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"2277","name":"Galaxy Coney Island","violationCode":"3-304.12","violationDescription":"During pauses in FOOD preparation or dispensing, UTENSILS shall be stored:\r\n(A) In the FOOD with their handles above the top of the FOOD and the container;\r\n(B) In FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS with their handles above the      top of the FOOD within containers or EQUIPMENT that can be closed, such as      bins of sugar, flour, or cinnamon;\r\n(C) On a clean portion of the FOOD preparation table or cooking EQUIPMENT\r\n(D)  In running water, such as dipper well.\r\n(E)  In a clean, protected location if the UTENSILS, such as ice scoops, are   used only with a FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS; or\r\n(F)  In a container of water maintained at a temperature of at least 135° F.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Dispensing utensil(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Improperly stored","subProblem":"In standing water","location":"COOKING AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2018-05-08T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store as stated above."},{"inspectionid":"42225","inspectionDate":"5/8/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"2277","name":"Galaxy Coney Island","violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\r\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\r\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"COOKING AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Store below 41 degrees F."}]},{"inspectionid":"40477","establishmentid":"2277","name":"Galaxy Coney Island","inspectionDate":"2017-10-11T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"112","pcount":"3","pfcount":"1","ccount":"1","criticalcount":"4","noncritical":"1","correctedcritical":"4","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"40477","inspectionDate":"10/11/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"2277","name":"Galaxy Coney Island","violationCode":"3-301.11","violationDescription":"(A) To prevent food contamination FOOD EMPLOYEES shall properly wash their      hands.\r\n(B) FOOD EMPLOYEES may not contact exposed, READY-TO-EAT FOOD with      their bare hands and shall use suitable UTENSILS such as deli tissue,       spatulas, tongs, single-use gloves, or dispensing EQUIPMENT. (P)\r\n(C) FOOD EMPLOYEES shall minimize bare hand and arm contact with exposed     FOOD that is not in a READY-TO-EAT form. (Pf)\r\n\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Employee(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Handled with bare hands","subProblem":"","location":"COOKING AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-10-11T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Suitable utensils or single-use gloves are to be utilized."},{"inspectionid":"40477","inspectionDate":"10/11/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"2277","name":"Galaxy Coney Island","violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\r\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\r\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"COOKING AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-10-19T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store below 41 degrees F."},{"inspectionid":"40477","inspectionDate":"10/11/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"2277","name":"Galaxy Coney Island","violationCode":"3-304.12","violationDescription":"During pauses in FOOD preparation or dispensing, UTENSILS shall be stored:\r\n(A) In the FOOD with their handles above the top of the FOOD and the container;\r\n(B) In FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS with their handles above the      top of the FOOD within containers or EQUIPMENT that can be closed, such as      bins of sugar, flour, or cinnamon;\r\n(C) On a clean portion of the FOOD preparation table or cooking EQUIPMENT\r\n(D)  In running water, such as dipper well.\r\n(E)  In a clean, protected location if the UTENSILS, such as ice scoops, are   used only with a FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS; or\r\n(F)  In a container of water maintained at a temperature of at least 135° F.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Dispensing utensil(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Improperly stored","subProblem":"In standing water","location":"COOKING AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2017-10-19T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store as stated above."},{"inspectionid":"40477","inspectionDate":"10/11/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"2277","name":"Galaxy Coney Island","violationCode":"3-302.11","violationDescription":"(A) FOOD shall be protected from cross contamination by:  \r\n(1) Except as specified in (1)(c) below, separating raw animal FOODS during         storage, preparation, holding, and display from:\r\n(a) Raw READY-TO-EAT FOOD including other raw animal FOOD such as FISH for sushi or MOLLUSCAN SHELLFISH, or other raw READY-TO-EAT FOOD such as fruits and vegetables,(P) and\r\n(b) Cooked READY-TO-EAT FOOD; (P)\r\n(c) Frozen, commercially processed and packaged raw animal FOOD may be          stored or displayed with or above frozen, commercially processed and           packaged, ready-to-eat food.\r\n(2) Except when combined as ingredients, separating types of raw animal FOODS    from each other such as beef, FISH, lamb, pork, and POULTRY during storage,        preparation, holding, and display by:\r\n(a) Using separate EQUIPMENT for each type, (P) or\r\n(b) Arranging each type of FOOD in EQUIPMENT so that cross contamination of one type with another is prevented, (P) and\r\n(c) Preparing each type of FOOD at different times or in separate areas; (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Raw animal food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored over/next to","subProblem":"Raw ready-to-eat food(s)","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-10-11T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store raw animal foods below and away from foods needing little or no further prep."},{"inspectionid":"40477","inspectionDate":"10/11/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"2277","name":"Galaxy Coney Island","violationCode":"3-501.17","violationDescription":"(A)  READY-TO-EAT, POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  prepared and held refrigerated for more than 24 hours in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT  shall be clearly marked at the time of preparation to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\r\n(B)  A container of refrigerated, commercially prepared READY-TO-EAT POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  shall be clearly marked, at the time the original container is opened in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT, to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\r\n\r\nA date marking system that does not exceed 7 days, including date of preparation, or opening is to be used. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Commercially processed ready to eat potentially hazardous food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Without date of consumption marking","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-10-11T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Datemark with a discard date of 7 days or less."}]},{"inspectionid":"38697","establishmentid":"2277","name":"Galaxy Coney Island","inspectionDate":"2017-05-12T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"112","pcount":"2","pfcount":"2","ccount":"2","criticalcount":"4","noncritical":"2","correctedcritical":"0","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"38697","inspectionDate":"5/12/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"2277","name":"Galaxy Coney Island","violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\r\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\r\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Store below 41 degrees F."},{"inspectionid":"38697","inspectionDate":"5/12/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"2277","name":"Galaxy Coney Island","violationCode":"4-601.11","violationDescription":"(A) EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be clean to sight and touch. (Pf)\r\n(B) The FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of cooking EQUIPMENT and pans shall be kept free of encrusted grease deposits and other soil accumulations. \r\n(C) NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be kept free of an accumulation of dust, dirt, FOOD residue, and other debris. \r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Food-contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean."},{"inspectionid":"38697","inspectionDate":"5/12/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"2277","name":"Galaxy Coney Island","violationCode":"3-501.17","violationDescription":"(A)  READY-TO-EAT, POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  prepared and held refrigerated for more than 24 hours in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT  shall be clearly marked at the time of preparation to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\r\n(B)  A container of refrigerated, commercially prepared READY-TO-EAT POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  shall be clearly marked, at the time the original container is opened in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT, to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\r\n\r\nA date marking system that does not exceed 7 days, including date of preparation, or opening is to be used. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"In house prepared ready-to-eat potentially hazardous  food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Without date of consumption marking","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Datemark with a discard date of 7 days or less."},{"inspectionid":"38697","inspectionDate":"5/12/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"2277","name":"Galaxy Coney Island","violationCode":"3-304.12","violationDescription":"During pauses in FOOD preparation or dispensing, UTENSILS shall be stored:\r\n(A) In the FOOD with their handles above the top of the FOOD and the container;\r\n(B) In FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS with their handles above the      top of the FOOD within containers or EQUIPMENT that can be closed, such as      bins of sugar, flour, or cinnamon;\r\n(C) On a clean portion of the FOOD preparation table or cooking EQUIPMENT\r\n(D)  In running water, such as dipper well.\r\n(E)  In a clean, protected location if the UTENSILS, such as ice scoops, are   used only with a FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS; or\r\n(F)  In a container of water maintained at a temperature of at least 135° F.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Dispensing utensil(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Improperly stored","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Relocate."},{"inspectionid":"38697","inspectionDate":"5/12/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"2277","name":"Galaxy Coney Island","violationCode":"MFL289.2129","violationDescription":"Sec. 2129. (1) All of the following food establishments shall employ a minimum of 1 managerial employee who is currently certified under a personnel certification program accredited by the American national standards institute, utilizing the conference for food protection standards:  (a) A food service establishment that is not any of the following:    (i) Operating under a temporary food service establishment license.  (ii) A vending machine location.     (b) An extended retail food establishment.  (c) Operated within a retail grocery.  (2) An individual certified under subsection (1) shall be recognized with full faith and credit by the state and all local units of government throughout the state.  (3) The department may promulgate rules to do all of the following:  (a) Develop requirements for retail food establishments to follow when employing certified food safety managers or personnel.  (b) Set a reasonable date for compliance with the requirements under subdivision (a) taking into consideration existing local personnel certification requirements.  (c) Establish certification fees necessary to implement, maintain, and track certified individuals directly or by contract. The department may annually adjust the schedule of fees to provide that the fee charged is sufficient to cover the cost of the certification tracking program.  (d) Implement and enforce the requirements described in subdivision (a).    (4) The certification program developed by the American national standards institute, as it exists on April 1, 2008 , is incorporated by reference. The department may adopt updates to the certification program accreditation standards in subsection (1) by rule.     (5) This section does not prohibit any local legislative body from implementing a food handler program, an employee health certification program, or a manager certification program, if it is not in conflict with this section.","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Person-in-charge","subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"ESTABLISHMENT","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"inspectionid":"38697","inspectionDate":"5/12/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"2277","name":"Galaxy Coney Island","violationCode":"3-301.11","violationDescription":"(A) To prevent food contamination FOOD EMPLOYEES shall properly wash their      hands.\r\n(B) FOOD EMPLOYEES may not contact exposed, READY-TO-EAT FOOD with      their bare hands and shall use suitable UTENSILS such as deli tissue,       spatulas, tongs, single-use gloves, or dispensing EQUIPMENT. (P)\r\n(C) FOOD EMPLOYEES shall minimize bare hand and arm contact with exposed     FOOD that is not in a READY-TO-EAT form. (Pf)\r\n\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Food item(s) handled","subItem":"","problemDescription":"With soiled/contaminated hands/arms","subProblem":"","location":"COOKING AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Hands/arms shall be washed with soap and hot water at handsink."}]},{"inspectionid":"37209","establishmentid":"2277","name":"Galaxy Coney Island","inspectionDate":"2016-11-09T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"112","pcount":"2","pfcount":"0","ccount":"1","criticalcount":"2","noncritical":"1","correctedcritical":"2","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"37209","inspectionDate":"11/9/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"2277","name":"Galaxy Coney Island","violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"The Cold table","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2016-11-15T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"inspectionid":"37209","inspectionDate":"11/9/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"2277","name":"Galaxy Coney Island","violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\r\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\r\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"The Cold table","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2016-11-15T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store below 41 degrees F."},{"inspectionid":"37209","inspectionDate":"11/9/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"2277","name":"Galaxy Coney Island","violationCode":"7-204.11","violationDescription":"Chemical SANITIZERS and other chemical antimicrobials applied to FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES shall meet the requirements specified in this code. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Sanitizer(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Do not comply with law","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2016-11-09T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null}]}]}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"2277"}}